dia.com 2018-10-02

# Privacy Policy | Dia&Co

## 1\. Introduction

Thank you for visiting dia.com, operated by Dia&Co. Dia.com is a consumer e-commerce website that provides online personal styling for women sizes 14-32. This privacy policy applies to the dia.com website only. Please read this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions carefully, as by using our Website you agree to be bound by both documents. 

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us via email at privacy@dia.com. 

## 2\. Definitions

In this Privacy Policy, we use the following definitions: 

  * "dia.com" or "we" or "us" refers to our company, known as "Dia&Co"; our Website; our Service; or a combination of all or some of the preceding definitions, depending on the context in which the word is used; 
  * "Service" refers to the services that we provide through our Website, including our styling and apparel selections, and the Website itself; 
  * "Website" refers to our website, www.dia.com; 
  * "User" and "You" refer to anyone who uses our Website. 

## 3\. Information Collected 

_Personally Identifying Information_

We collect certain personal information from you when you sign up to our Service and/or engage in transactions via dia.com, including through your account, through your posting on our social media page, or through our chat service, that can be used to identify you, such as your first and last name, e-mail address, mailing address, shipping address, credit card information, telephone number, social media handles, images, and photographs. 

_Customer Data_

We collect information about your purchases, returns, likes and dislikes, and similar activity when you use our Service. 

_Payment Information_

We use a third-party service to receive payments. We do not process, record or maintain your credit card information; that is handled entirely by our payment services vendor. 

_Gift Cards_

If you purchase a gift card, we will collect the Personally Identifying Information about you and about the recipient that is necessary to process the purchase and to deliver the gift card. 

_Referrals and Social Networking Websites_

We may also collect information about your friends to whom you refer dia.com using our referral service. 

Finally, our Website enables you to connect to accounts that you may have on social networking sites. By connecting to those accounts, you authorize us to access your account(s) on such social networking site(s) and see the information that you have provided to those sites. 

_Non-Personally Identifiable Information_

Our Website also collects certain other information, such as your IP address, information collected by "cookies," and purchase history that does not itself necessarily identify you but could do so if it were to be combined with sufficient other information. 

In addition, whenever you visit our Website, we collect other information from you, such as your referring URL, pages viewed, length of visit, browser, operating system, and Internet Service Provider.  We also collect information about your dress size and style preferences in order to select items for you. Without additional information, this information alone cannot usually be used to identify you. 

## 4\. Use of Personal and Other Information

The information we collect from you, to the extent that it is private, is used and/or disclosed only in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

Comments that you make to your stylist are not made publicly viewable. 

We use your personal information to verify your registration, to provide you with the styling, the Box, and other services available through our Website, to process your transactions, and to provide and ship products to you. We will use the email address you provided to us to communicate with you about your transactions and to respond to your inquiries. 

In addition, we may use your Personally Identifying Information and/or Customer Data: 

  * To enhance or improve User experience, our Website, or our Service. 
  * To send e-mails about our products and services. 
  * Use photographs that you have uploaded and reviews and comments that you have posted to our Website for marketing purposes; 
  * To perform any other function that we believe in good faith is necessary to protect the security or proper functioning of our Website. 
  * To respond when required by subpoena, warrant or other legal process. 

_Aggregated Data_

We generate aggregated tracking information for traffic accounting and content analysis. Such aggregated information is not directly linked to any personal information and cannot be used to identify you or any individual user of our Website. We may share this aggregated information with other companies to help understand how our Website is used. 

Once you register with dia.com, we will retain your registration and associated information for as long as they remain registered. If you choose to cancel your registration, we will retain your order records but will delete other information that you have provided within a reasonable time thereafter if you so request. 

## 5\. Accessing, Editing, and Removing Personally Identifying Information

You may review and edit the Personally Identifying Information you have provided to us by logging into your registered account on the Website and editing your account information. 

## 6\. Cookies

Like most websites, we use "cookies" – small data files stored on your computer -- to help provide you with a personalized and enhanced online experience by actions such as remembering your preferences, tracking advertisements, and remembering your shopping cart items.  Depending on the purpose, we may use both session and permanent cookies. For these reasons, you need to enable cookies in your browser. If you choose not to accept cookies, you will not be able to use certain features of our Website. 

Our Website currently does not respond to so-called "Do Not Track" signals sent by some browsers. 

## 7\. Links to Third Party Websites

Dia.com provides links to third-party websites such as Pinterest, Facebook, and Instagram. Those websites have their own privacy policies that may differ substantially from ours. Please review the privacy policy and terms of service for each site you visit through such links. 

## 8\. Third-Party Access to and Sharing of Personal Information

Dia.com uses other companies to provide support to our Website and our Services, and we must share your personal information and transactional information with these companies, or they may collect your personal information directly, so that they can provide their services to us and ultimately to you. For example, we use a third-party company to host our site and another third-party company to process your payments. Our contracts with those companies prohibit those companies from making use of your Personally Identifying Information for any purpose other than to assist our Site and Service. 

Your payments are handled by a third-party payment processor. By making a purchase on the Site, you authorize us to collect, share, and otherwise use your information in conjunction with our payment processor. All credit-card information is stored by our payment processor; dia.com itself does not retain credit card numbers. 

  * We may combine your Personally Identifying Information and Customer Data with other information about you (such as demographic information and past purchase history) available from our records and other sources. This information will be used to make our future marketing efforts more efficient. 
  * Your Personally Identifying Information and Customer Data may also be shared with our third party service providers that assist us with our marketing efforts and with other marketers whose products or services we believe may be of interest to you. If you prefer that we do not share your name and address with other marketers, please email us at privacy@dia.com. 

Dia.com may co-market its products with those of other companies, or we may rent or sell information about you, including your Personally Identifying Information and Customer Data, to other companies that offer products that may be of interest to you. Such other companies will receive your email and/or mailing address and other Personally Identifying Information and, occasionally, Customer Data. 

You can direct us not to share your Personally Identifying Information and Customer Data with such other companies by sending us an email to privacy@dia.com. 

Finally, in the event our Website or company is sold or restructured, the personal information that we have collected about you will be transferred to the acquiring company. The acquiring company will assume the rights and obligations regarding your personal information as described in this privacy policy. 

## 9\. Release of Your Information for Legal Purposes

At times Dia&Co may be required by law to release information about you in response to a legal request from a government agency or a private litigant. In the event that we receive a subpoena affecting your privacy, we may elect to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either, and in certain cases we may be prohibited from notifying you. We also reserve the right to report you, and release personal information about you to, law enforcement or other appropriate third parties where we believe that it is prudent to do so for legal reasons, such as our belief that you have engaged in fraudulent activities. 

If you are a New Jersey consumer, the terms of this Section 9 do not limit or waive your rights as a consumer under New Jersey law and the provisions in this Privacy Policy are intended to be only as broad and inclusive as is permitted by the laws of the State of New Jersey. 

## 10\. Commercial and Non-Commercial Communications

By providing us with your contact information, you authorize us to contact you regarding your use of the Website, including any transactions in which you engage. You may unsubscribe from certain commercial email communications by opting out from them. 

If you are a New Jersey consumer, the terms of this Section 10 do not limit or waive your rights as a consumer under New Jersey law and the provisions in this Privacy Policy are intended to be only as broad and inclusive as is permitted by the laws of the State of New Jersey. 

## 11\. Our Policies Regarding Children

We do not collect or maintain information from those under the age of 13, and do not knowingly do so. 

## 12\. Security Measures

We have established and implemented written data security policies and procedures that we believe are appropriate for our current business practices. We take certain measures to enhance the security of our Website, and review and update our security measures as appropriate. 

## 13\. Your California Privacy Rights

Under _California Business and Professions Code §§_ 22575-22579, California residents may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to any third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year. To make such a request, please contact us at privacy@dia.com or write to us at 175 Varick Street, 7th Floor, New York, NY 10014. 

You may contact us at privacy@dia.com with any questions. 

## 14\. International Users

Our Site is designed and targeted for Users in the United States, and adheres to United States privacy laws. If you are using this Site while in another nation, please be advised that dia.com transfers Personally Identifying Information to the United States and that any such information that you submit to us is governed by U.S. law. 

## 15\. Amendments

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we amend this Privacy Policy, we will update this page accordingly. Any such amendments will be effective immediately upon posting unless stated otherwise. Your continued use of our Website following the posting of an amended Privacy Policy means you agree to any such changes. 

Effective Date: June 24, 2018
